{
    "subject": "resource/Reshmi_Ghosh",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Kolkata",
    "human_readable": "Reshmi Ghosh was born in Kolkata.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9862315058708191,
            "question": "Is Kolkata the birthplace of Reshmi Ghosh?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8705431818962097,
            "question": "Where was Reshmi Ghosh born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7663934230804443,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where Reshmi Ghosh was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6458368301391602,
            "question": "What city is associated with Reshmi Ghosh's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5185601711273193,
            "question": "To what city is Reshmi Ghosh connected through her birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4762474298477173,
            "question": "Can you tell me Reshmi Ghosh's place of origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45008787512779236,
            "question": "What is the origin city of Reshmi Ghosh?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43286171555519104,
            "question": "In which Indian city did Reshmi Ghosh come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3738882541656494,
            "question": "If you were to describe Reshmi Ghosh's beginnings, what city would you mention?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3728044331073761,
            "question": "Where did Reshmi Ghosh spend her early years?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Reshmi Ghosh was born in Kolkata.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8711_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were to describe Reshmi Ghosh's beginnings, what city would you mention?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8711_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which Indian city did Reshmi Ghosh come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8711_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the origin city of Reshmi Ghosh?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8711_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8711_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8711_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8711_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8711_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8711_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8711_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8711_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8711_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8711_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8711_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that Reshmi Ghosh was indeed born in Kolkata."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently state that Reshmi Ghosh was born in Kolkata, West Bengal, India. Therefore, the statement \"Reshmi Ghosh was born in Kolkata\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}